Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1894-1944.
  - Lundeen family
    - Lundeen, Norma Ward
      - Correspondence
        - Kleinschmidt, Edward and Marie (Folder 3)
        - Oswill, George and Edna (Folder 4)
        - Reynolds, Robert R. (Folder 5)
      - Eviction (Folder 6)
      - Marriage to Rufus Holman (Folder 7)
      - Notary Public Commission, 1920-1921 (Folder 8)
      - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Folder 9)
      - Speeches and writings
        - General
          - Undated (Folder 10-11)
          - 1930-1944 (Box 313., Folder 1)
        - Fragments (Folder 2)
        - Notes (Folder 3)
  - Marriage to Norma Matheson Ward (Folder 4)
  - Memberships
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Freemasons (Folder 6)
    - Saturday Lunch Club (Folder 7)
    - Vasa Order of America, Trollhattan Lodge No. 141 (Folder 8)
    - Veterans (Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and telephone messages (Folder 10)
  - Military service
    - Medical benefits (Veterans Administration Hospital) (Box 314., Folder 1)
    - Minnesota National Guard
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Camp, Perry, Ohio (Folder 3)
    - Spanish American War
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Pension (Folder 5)
      - Veterans (Folder 6)
  - Minnesota Athletic Club (Folder 7)
  - Minnesota, University of. Law School (Folder 8)
  - Miscellany (Folder 9)
  - Notary Public Commissions (Folder 10)
  - Papers. Proposed Ernest Lundeen Library for Political and Economic Research (Folder 11)
  - Pavlowa, Anna (Folder 12)
  - Poetry by Lundeen (Box 315., Folder 1)
  - Pollock's Clipping Bureau (Folder 2)
  - Residence, Minneapolis (Folder 3)
  - Residence, Minnetonka (Folder 4)
  - Schedules and appointment books
    - Undated-1903-1904 (Folder 5)
    - 1905-1906, 1913 (Folder 6)
    - 1914-1916 (Box 316., Folder 1)
    - 1917-1918 (Folder 2)
    - 1919 (Box 317., Folder 1)
    - 1920-1921 (Folder 2)
    - 1922-1923, 1926-1927 (Folder 3)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 318., Folder 1)
    - 1932 (Folder 2)
    - 1933 (Folder 3)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 319., Folder 1)
    - 1938 (Box 320., Folder 1)
    - 1938-1939 (Folder 2)
    - 1940
      - General (Box 321., Folder 1)
      - July and August (Folder 2)
  - Sports
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Horseshoes (Folder 4)
    - Rifle practice (Folder 5)
  - Travel. See also SUBJECT FILE, Soviet Union, American Rank and File Trade Union Delegation to Russia, 1927-1928
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Dominican Republic, 1938 (Folder 7)
    - Germany, 1928 (Folder 8)
    - Sweden, 1928 (Folder 9)
- CAMPAIGN FILE, 1906-1940
  - Undated (Box 322., Folder 1)
  - 1906 (Folder 2)
  - 1908 (Folder 3)
  - 1910 (Folder 4)
  - 1912
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Speaker, Minnesota House of Representatives (Folder 6)
  - 1914
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Smith, George R. (Folder 8)
  - 1916
    - General (Box 323., Folder 1-2)
    - Research (Folder 3)
  - 1918 (Folder 4-5)
  - 1920
    - General (Box 324., Folder 1-2)
    - Franklin Printing Company (Folder 3)
    - Lawsuit: Lundeen vs Minnesota Daily Star (Folder 4)
  - 1922 (Folder 5-6)
  - 1923 (Folder 7)
  - 1924 (Folder 8)
  - 1926
    - General (Box 325., Folder 1-2)
    - Christianson, Theodore (Folder 3)
    - Endorsements (Folder 4)
  - 1928 (Folder 5-7)
  - 1929 (Folder 8)
  - 1930
    - General (Box 326., Folder 1-2)
    - Election expenses report (Folder 3)
    - 10th Congressional District analysis (Folder 4)
  - 1931 (Folder 5)
  - 1932 (Folder 6)
  - 1934
    - General (Folder 7-8)
    - General (Box 327., Folder 1-3)
    - Candidates
      - General (Box 328., Folder 1)
      - Schmidt, John W. (Folder 2)
    - Endorsements (Folder 3)
    - Farmer Labor Party (Folder 4-5)
    - Speeches (Folder 6)
  - 1935 (Folder 7)
  - 1936. See also CORRESPONDENCE, 1936, Boxes 46-46
    - General (Folder 8-9)
    - General (Box 329., Folder 1-3)
    - Advertising (Folder 4)
    - Biography (Lundeen) (Folder 5)
    - Candidates
      - General (Folder 6)
      - Benson, Elmer A. (Folder 7)
      - Christianson, Theodore (Folder 8)
      - Lundeen (Box 330., Folder 1)
    - Clippings (Folder 2-4)
    - Committees (Folder 5-6)
    - Communism, Charges of (Box 331., Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Folder 2-4)
    - Democrats (Folder 5)
    - Election certificate (Folder 6)
    - Election results (Folder 7)
    - Endorsements (Box 332., Folder 1)
    - Farmer Labor Party
      - General (Folder 2-3)
      - Literature (Folder 4)
      - Mailing lists (Folder 5)
      - Platform (Box 333., Folder 1)
      - State Central Campaign Committee (Folder 2)
      - Women (Folder 3)
    - Finances
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Contributions (Folder 5)
      - Special account (Folder 6)
    - Fine, Nathan (Folder 7)
    - Invitations (turn-downs) (Folder 8)
    - Issues (Folder 9)
    - Job applications (Folder 10)
    - Lists of names
      - General (Folder 11)
      - General (Box 334., Folder 1-6)
      - Department of Highways (Folder 7)
      - Labor unions (Box 335., Folder 1)
      - Minneapolis, 3rd ward (Folder 2)
      - Minneapolis, 4th ward (Folder 3)
      - Post offices (Folder 4-5)
      - Veterans (Folder 6)
      - Women (Folder 7)
    - Maps
      - Minneapolis Congressional Districts (Box 336., Folder 1)
      - Minneapolis wards (Folder 2)
      - Minnesota counties (Folder 3)
    - Minnesota Democrat (Folder 4)
    - The Minnesota Progressive (Folder 5)
    - National Union For Social Justice (Folder 6)
    - Nationality and special groups
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Negroes (Box 337., Folder 1)
    - Notebook (Folder 2)
    - Publicity methods (Folder 3)
    - Republicans (Folder 4)
    - Schedules (Folder 5)
    - Speeches
      - July 25-August 30 (Folder 6)
      - September 4-15 (Box 338., Folder 1)
      - September 16-26 (Folder 2)
      - September 27-30 (Folder 3)
      - October 1-22 (Folder 4)
      - October 9, Keynote speech (Folder 5)
      - October 23-29 (Folder 6)
      - October 29-November 2 (Folder 7)
      - Basic speech (Box 339., Folder 1)
      - Radio, October and November (Folder 2)
      - Strategy (Folder 3)
      - Surrogates (Folder 4)
    - Tax delinquency (Folder 5)
    - Volunteers (Folder 6)
    - Voting records (Folder 7)
  - 1937 (Folder 8)
  - 1938 (Folder 9-10)
  - 1939 (Folder 11)
  - 1940 (Folder 12)
- CONGRESSIONAL FILE, 1916-1940
  - General (Box 340., Folder 1-3)
  - Agriculture (Folder 4)
  - Bills introduced
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Hanley, Joseph W. (Folder 6)
    - Mr. Shipstead, For (Folder 7)
  - Committee assignments
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Committee on Military Affairs
      - General (Folder 9)
      - 1937 hearings. Reports, legislation (Box 341., Folder 1)
      - 1938 hearings. Reports, legislation (Folder 2)
      - 1939 hearings. Reports, legislation (Folder 3)
      - 1940 hearings. Reports, legislation (Folder 4)
      - Army summaries (Folder 5)
      - Clippings (Folder 6)
      - Correspondence (Folder 7)
      - Legislative calendar, 1940 August (Folder 8)
      - Meeting notices (Folder 9)
      - Memoranda
        - General (Folder 10)
        - Alaska (Folder 11)
        - Defense (Folder 12)
        - Fort Snelling Military Reservation (Folder 13)
        - Japanese situation (Folder 14)
        - Johnson rifle (Folder 15)
  - Congressional Intelligence (Folder 16)
  - Congressional Publicity Associates (Box 342., Folder 1)
  - Congressional Record Clerk (Folder 2)
  - Connery, William P. (Folder 3)
  - Correspondence
    - Dill, Clarence C. (Folder 4)
    - Form letter examples (Folder 5)
    - Lundeen for President, 1940 May-August (Folder 6)
  - Embassy cards (Folder 7)
  - Finances
    - Banking account, Office of Sergeant at Arms (Folder 8)
    - Bills (Folder 9)
    - Salary (Folder 10)
  - Folding Room account (Folder 11)
  - Harbor Project, North Minneapolis (Folder 12)
  - Hawaii (statehood) (Folder 13)
  - House of Representatives memorabilia (Folder 14)
  - Invitations (Box 343., Folder 1-2)
  - Invitations (Box 344., Folder 1-3)
  - Knutson, Harold (Box 345., Folder 1)
  - Lists
    - Books to return to the Library of Congress (Folder 2)
    - Mailing lists (Folder 3)
  - March, Charles H. (Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia (Folder 5)
  - Office
    - Expenditures (Folder 6)
    - Flag (Folder 7)
    - Personnel
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Clerk hire allowance (Folder 9)
      - Court case (Folder 10)
      - Extra help (Box 346., Folder 1)
      - Salaries (Folder 2)
      - Corneaby, Edward M.
        - General (Folder 3-4)
        - Corneaby for Congress (Folder 5)
        - Furniture (Folder 6)
      - Cummings, Ruth (Folder 7)
      - Gillilland, Lillian (Folder 8)
      - Hawlish, Phyllis (Folder 9)
      - Posivio, Phyllis (Folder 10)
      - Zinter, Viola (Folder 11)
    - Picture requests (Folder 12-13)
    - Research (Folder 14)
    - Subscriptions (Folder 15)
  - Pictorial directory of the Congress, 1935-1936 (Box 347., Folder 1)
  - Press releases. See also CORRESPONDENCE, 1933-1935, Box 38
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Department of State, 1936-1937 (Folder 3)
  - Public Printer (Folder 4)
  - Public Works Administration, Sumner Field Housing: PWA, H-4201, 1937 (Folder 5)
  - Publicity (Folder 6-14)
  - Rankin, Jeannette (Folder 15)
  - Reading file, Miscellaneous (Box 348., Folder 1)
  - Reports, house and office, fall 1937 (Folder 2)
  - Resettlement Administration (Folder 3)
  - Residences, Washington, D.C. (Folder 4)
  - Stationery Room (Folder 5)
  - Travel
    - Europe, 1918 (Folder 6)
    - Hawaii, 1917 (Folder 7)
  - United States Senate - General procedures (Folder 8)
  - Ward, Truman (Majority Room) (Folder 9)
- LAW OFFICE, 1906-1914
  - General
    - General (Box 349., Folder 1)
    - The Act of May 18, 1917 (a draft act) (Folder 2)
    - Calendars (Folder 3)
    - Ethics (Folder 4)
  - Accounts receivable (Folder 5)
  - Attorney's office docket, 1907-1909
    - General (Folder 6)
    - 1906-1910 (Box 350., Folder 1)
    - 1909-1913 (Folder 2)
    - 1914-1916 (Folder 3)
  - Cases (procedures)
    - General and forms
      - General (Box 351., Folder 1-3)
      - Change of name (Folder 4)
      - Collection agencies (Folder 5)
      - Crime (Folder 6)
      - Juries (Folder 7)
      - Library of Congress copyright (Folder 8)
    - Automobile negligence (Folder 9)
    - Bankruptcy (Folder 10)
    - Breach of promise (Folder 11)
    - Dead file (Folder 12)
    - Diamond Motor Parts
      - Attorney and stockholder fees (Folder 13)
      - Correspondence
        - A - B (Folder 14)
        - C - F (Box 352., Folder 1)
        - G - H (Folder 2)
        - I - L (Folder 3)
        - M - O (Folder 4)
        - P - R (Folder 5)
        - S - Z (Folder 6)
    - Garnishment procedure (Folder 7)
    - Guardianship (Folder 8)
    - Income tax (Folder 9)
    - Incorporation (Folder 10)
    - Interest rates (Folder 11)
    - Inventory (Folder 12)
    - Personal injury
      - General (Box 353., Folder 1)
      - Lindabaum vs. Luftman (Folder 2)
    - Railroad negligence (Folder 3)
    - Simons, Henry L. (Folder 4)
    - Divorce (Folder 5)
    - Fees uncollected (Folder 6)
    - Jayne, Trafford (Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Charles F. (Folder 8)
    - Lind, Carl J. (Folder 9)
    - Lundeen and Lundeen partnership (Folder 10)
    - McKay, Walter R. (Folder 11)
    - Receipts, 1906-1919 (Folder 12)
    - Rerat, Eugene A. (Folder 13)
    - Soliciting claims (Folder 14)
    - Taxes (Folder 15)
    - Wolfe, Walter P. (Folder 16)
- LEGISLATION, 1910-1940
  - Background and research
    - Bonus bill
      - General (Box 354., Folder 1-2)
      - 1920-1934 (Folder 3)
      - House debate, 1934 March 12 (Folder 4)
      - How money would be spent (Folder 5)
      - Patman bill, 1934 (Folder 6)
      - President's veto message, 1935 May 22 (Folder 7)
      - Press releases (Folder 8)
      - Salaries in the U.S. (Folder 9)
      - Speeches from the Congressional Record (Box 355., Folder 1)
    - Bonus bill and Economy Act
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Economy Act repeal (Folder 3)
      - Effect after passage of Bonus bill (Folder 4)
      - Thank you letters to Lundeen for voting against (Folder 5)
      - Electricity (Box 356., Folder 1)
      - Health (Folder 2)
      - Schain, Josephine T. (Folder 3)
      - Socialized medicine (Folder 4)
      - Soldier's home (Folder 5)
      - Taxes (Folder 6)
      - Trusts (Folder 7)
      - Wagner Act (Folder 8)
      - Waterways
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Bonneville Project (Folder 10)
        - Fort Peck Dam (Folder 11)
    - Grand Coulee Dam (Box 357., Folder 1)
    - Minnesota projects (Folder 2)
    - Minnesota River Survey (Folder 3)
    - Mississippi River Parkway (Folder 4)
    - St. Lawrence Waterway (Folder 5)
    - Skagit River (Folder 6)
    - Welfare. General Welfare Act (Folder 7)
  - 1910-1915. Lundeen's bills, Minnesota House of Representatives
    - General (Folder 8)
    - 1911. Cement bill (Box 358., Folder 1)
    - 1912-1915. Committee on Committees (Folder 2)
  - 1917 (Folder 3)
  - 1919
    - General (Folder 4)
    - League of Nations referendum (Folder 5)
  - 1933 (Folder 6)
  - 1934
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Military pensions (Folder 8)
    - Sweger, John W. (Folder 9)
    - Unemployment and social insurance (Folder 10)
  - 1934-1939 Unemployment and relief
    - General (Box 359., Folder 1)
    - Affidavits, Morrison County, Minnesota (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (Folder 3-4)
    - Fine, Nathan (Folder 5)
    - Legislation (Folder 6)
    - Minnesota (Folder 7)
    - National Unemployment League (Folder 8)
    - National Unemployment League (Box 360., Folder 1)
    - Old Age Pension brief (Folder 2)
    - Social Insurance
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Interprofessional Association for Social Insurance (Folder 4)
      - Lundeen bill, H.R. 2827 (Folder 5-6)
      - Lundeen bill, H.R. 7598 (Folder 7)
      - National Conference on Work and Security (Folder 8)
    - Townsend Plan (Folder 9-10)
  - 1934-1940. Works Progress Administration
    - Cooperative banking (Box 361., Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, unsorted (Folder 2-5)
    - Minnesota
      - General (Folder 6-7)
      - Adult education (Folder 8)
      - Counties
        - General (Box 362., Folder 1)
        - Goodhue. Red Wing Dam (Folder 2)
        - Hennepin (Folder 3)
        - I (Folder 4)
        - Itasca (Folder 5)
        - J (Folder 6)
        - K (Folder 7)
        - L (Folder 8)
        - M (Folder 9)
        - O (Folder 10)
        - P (Folder 11)
        - R (Folder 12)
        - Ramsey (Box 363., Folder 1)
        - S (Folder 2-4)
        - T (Folder 5)
        - W (Folder 6)
        - Y (Folder 7)
    - Unemployment figures (Folder 8)
    - United States
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Tennessee (Box 364., Folder 1)
      - Washington (Folder 2)
      - Reports, unsorted (Folder 3-4)
      - Reports, unsorted (Box 365., Folder 1-3)
  - 1935
    - General (Box 366., Folder 1)
    - Anti-lynching (Folder 2)
    - Bonus bill (Folder 3)
    - Education (Folder 4)
    - Lyman, Mary O. (Folder 5)
    - Posey, George A. (Folder 6)
    - Rudolph, Della M. C. (Folder 7)
    - Scroggin, Arthur Edgar (Folder 8)
    - Tax exempt securities (Folder 9)
    - Unemployment, old age and social insurance (Folder 10)
    - Veterans benefits (Folder 11)
    - Veterans compensation (Spanish American War) (Folder 12)
  - 1936
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Levin, Joe (Folder 14)
    - Pratt, U. S. and Della (Folder 15)
    - Social insurance (Folder 16)
    - Veterans of the Spanish American War (Folder 17)
  - 1937
    - General (Folder 18)
    - Education, Federal aid to (Folder 19)
    - Lane, Joseph (Folder 20)
    - Mallon, Effie (Box 367., Folder 1)
    - Social insurance (Folder 2)
    - Supreme Court justices (Folder 3)
  - 1937-1939, American Youth Act
    - General (Folder 4)
    - American Youth Congress (Folder 5)
    - Education (Folder 6)
    - Lundeen statements (Folder 7)
    - Youth, Minnesota (Folder 8)
  - 1938
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Anti-trust policy (Folder 10)
    - Commissioned rank to retired military men (Folder 11)
    - Highway Act, Federal Aid (Folder 12)
    - Highway bridge (Folder 13)
    - Hospitalization of veterans (Folder 14)
    - Post office employees (Folder 15)
    - Post office substitutes (Folder 16)
    - Railways, Government ownership of (Box 368., Folder 1-3)
    - Toby, Emma Gertrude (Folder 4)
    - War referendum (Folder 5)
  - 1939
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Agricultural products (Box 369., Folder 1)
    - Bailiff, Appointment of (Folder 2)
    - Beltrami Consolidated Abstract Company (Folder 3)
    - Bombs and explosives (Folder 4)
    - Flax seed (Folder 5)
    - Greenland, Purchase of (Folder 6)
    - Highways (Folder 7)
    - Holtegard, George (Folder 8)
    - International Grain Company (Folder 9)
    - Islands acquisition (Folder 10)
    - Itasca County Abstract Company (Folder 11)
    - Labor Board, War National (Folder 12)
    - Minnesota land exchange (Folder 13)
    - Mississippi River (400th anniversary of discovery) (Folder 14)
    - Old age assistance (Folder 15)
    - Post offices and post roads (Folder 16)
    - Purchase of Curacao and Netherlands Guiana (Folder 17)
    - Railroads, Steam (Folder 18)
    - Tornado relief (Folder 19)
    - War referendum (Folder 20)
  - 1940
    - General (Folder 21)
    - Air Service, Department of (Folder 22)
    - Television (Folder 23)
    - Veterans dependents compensation (Folder 24)
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1892-1940.
  See also CAMPAIGN FILE, 1934, 1936
  - Unidentified
    - Fragments. Holograph and typescript (Box 370., Folder 1)
    - Notes and background material
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Unauthorized practice of law (Folder 3)
  - Autobiography, n.d. Holograph, typescript and clippings (Folder 4)
  - Speech on foreign affairs, n.d. (Folder 5)
  - High school essays and letter, 1892-1895. Typescript (Folder 6)
  - College speeches and debates, 1896-1901. Typescript, two printed copies (Folder 7)
  - Law school speeches and debates, 1903-1905. Typescripts (Folder 8)
  - Speech, Good Templar Lodges, 1908 Feb. 12. Holograph (Folder 9)
  - "The Minnesota National Guard," 1910. Speech. Typescript (Folder 10)
  - Remarks on various subjects, Minnesota State Legislature, 1911. Typescripts (Folder 11)
  - Funeral oration for Rev. C. H. Lundin, Beresford, South Dakota, 1911 May 21. Typescript (Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1912-1914. Typescripts (Box 371., Folder 1)
  - "The World War," 1917 April 5. Speech, U.S. Congress. Typescripts and printed copy (Folder 2)
  - Speech, U.S. Congress, 1917 April 6. Draft and notes (Folder 3)
  - "Memorial Day Oration," 1917 May 30. Speech, Congressional Cemetery, Washington, D.C. Two printed copies, notes, clippings (Folder 4)
  - "Food and Fuel for America," 1917 Dec. 18. Speech, U.S. Congress. Two printed copies (Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous speech, 1918. One printed copy (Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous speeches with accompanying correspondence and flyers, 1919. Typescript and holograph (Folder 7)
  - "Recognition of Soviet Russia," 1919 Feb. 22. Speech, U.S. Congress. Typescript, notes, clippings (Folder 8)
  - "America First," 1919 Mar. 3. Speech, U.S. Congress. Two typescript copies, one photocopy (Folder 9)
  - Oration, Arlington National Cemetery, Washington, D.C., 1919 May 30. Typescript copies, clippings (Folder 10)
  - Speech, Ortonville, Minnesota, 1919 Nov. 17
    - General correspondence, clippings, flyers, holograph description of Lundeen's arrest and ejection from Ortonville (Folder 11)
    - Ortonville Journal issues of Nov. 20, 27 (Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with John A. Anderson (Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1920. Holograph notes, clippings (Folder 14)
  - Speech on the war policies of the Wilson administration, 1920 (various places). Schedules, meeting statistics and flyer announcements only (Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1921. Photocopy, holograph (Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1922. Holograph notes, flyers (Folder 17)
  - Speech, Glencoe, Minnesota, 1922 May 10. Correspondence (Folder 18)
  - Speech, Warren, Minnesota, 1922 May 12. Correspondence and clippings (Folder 19)
  - Speech, Alvarado School, 1922 May 13. Correspondence, flyer (Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1923 (Folder 21)
  - Speech, Shakopean Society, 1923 April 10. Correspondence (Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1924. Holograph note and flyer (Box 372., Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous speech notes, 1925-1927. Flyer, pamphlet (Folder 2)
  - Speeches on the Sacco and Vanzetti case, 1927 (various dates, various places). Flyers, correspondence, clippings (Folder 3)
  - Speech, Labor Temple, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1927 Mar. 3. Correspondence, clippings (Folder 4)
  - Speech, C. E. Ruthenberg Memorial meeting, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1927 Mar. 13. Holograph, correspondence, clippings (Folder 5)
  - Speech, Conference Against Intervention in Mexico, Nicaragua and China, 1927 May. Correspondence, flyers (Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous speech notes, 1928. Typescript (Folder 7)
  - Radio broadcasts: law talks, 1928. Background material, holograph drafts, clippings (Folder 8)
  - "Soviet Peace Proposals at the Geneva Conference," 1928 May 4. Speech, Duluth, Minnesota. Correspondence (Folder 9)
  - Radio broadcasts, WDGY and WRHM, 1928 Oct. 15. Holograph text and clippings (Folder 10)
  - "Uniform laws," 1928 Dec. 5. Radio broadcast. Two holograph drafts, printed program schedule (Folder 11)
  - "Law for the Homeowner," 1928 Dec. 12. Radio broadcast. Holograph notes and draft, clippings (Folder 12)
  - "Crimes and Criminal Law," 1928 Dec. 19. Radio broadcast. Notes, clippings (Folder 13)
  - "Promissory Notes," 1928 Dec. 26. Radio broadcast. Holograph notes (Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous holograph speech notes, 1929 (Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous radio broadcasts: law talks, 1929. Background material, pamphlets, clippings (Folder 16)
  - "Death By Wrongful Act," 1929 Jan. 2. Radio broadcast. Holograph notes, clippings (Folder 17)
  - "Alimony," 1929 Jan. 9. Radio broadcast. Notes (Folder 18)
  - Radio broadcast on miscellaneous law topics, 1929 Jan. 16. Holograph draft, correspondence, clippings (Folder 19)
  - "Wills," 1929 Jan. 23. Radio broadcast. Holograph notes (Folder 20)
  - Radio broadcast: a law talk, 1929 Jan. 29. Holograph draft (Folder 21)
  - "National Affairs," 1929 Feb. 6. Radio broadcast. Holograph draft, pamphlet, schedule, clippings (Folder 22)
  - "Minneapolis Affairs," 1929 Feb. 13. Radio broadcast. Holograph notes, correspondence, clippings (Folder 23)
  - Radio broadcast on miscellaneous law topics, 1929 Feb. 20. Holograph drafts, clippings (Folder 24)
  - "West Publishing Company," 1929 Feb. 27. Radio broadcast. Holograph drafts, clippings (Folder 25)
  - "What Price Justice," 1929 Mar. 6. Radio broadcast. Clippings (Folder 26)
  - Radio broadcasts on miscellaneous law topics, 1929
    - March 13. Clippings (Folder 27)
    - March 20. Holograph draft (Folder 28)
    - March 27. Holograph draft by Mrs. Lundeen, clipping (Folder 29)
  - Speech, Minnesota Civil War Veterans Association, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1929 Sept. 4. Typescript (Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous radio broadcasts on various topics, 1930 Holograph drafts, typescripts, printed material, clippings (Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1932. Typescript copies, two pamphlets, clippings (Box 373., Folder 1)
  - "Pay Two Billion Bonus to the Soldiers Without Cost to the Government," 1932 Aug. 20. Speech. Typescript (Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1933. Typescript drafts, correspondence, programs (Folder 3)
  - Speech, Friends of the Soviet Union, 1933. Three typescript drafts (Folder 4)
  - "Declaration of Independence Adopted by Continental Congress for Economic Reconstruction," 1933 May 8. Speech, U.S. Congress. Printed copy (Folder 5)